- do they stand out or in?
- Yes exactly.
Do they stand out or in?
Laura went really close, so she sees.
But what you see is something else from there, right?
Yes.
- Look!
- Yes.
It's moving.
- What is it under the table, then?
- If someone goes from the other side, we can see.
- You have no body, Alma.
- You'll eat me.
The head of the plate, just ... "Nam, Nam, Nam!"
"Say Cheese."
Check.
Laura is ready to eat Alma.
Let's see.
How good you are, Laura!
That went really well.
There you can sit for a while.
It is kind of a fraudulent face.
The camera does not look.
Only you see!
"Superpowers!"
(Super powers)
There you go.
- So!
And then I put some pillows on you here now.
- Okay.
Laura, move you so I can take a good card.
Hello there!
How are you in there?
Fun, of course!
Can I be the biggest once?
You will be huge.
"Oh my God!"
Laura, can't you go to Alma?
- Go to Alma once.
- Laura, come!
- She is very difficult to direct.
- Yes.
Check out, do you see there?
You can be very cute and small.
Come!
- Laura thinks it is fun to ride a slide.
- Yes, but exactly.
Fun!
So this is ames room.
Now I'm very big.